navimedix.com 2013-12-31

# Privacy Policy | NaviNet

INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE – NAVINET CORPORATE WEBSITE

At NaviNet, Inc., we recognize and respect the privacy of our website visitors. We do not collect personal information about visitors to the NaviNet corporate website unless it is provided voluntarily. If you send email inquiries to NaviNet, your personal information, including your email address, will be used only for the purpose of responding to your inquiry and will not be shared with third parties. Such information may be retained for the purpose of tracking the types of questions received by NaviNet.

For your convenience, the NaviNet corporate website contains links to other websites, including some sites administered by NaviNet, as well as to sites unrelated to NaviNet. This privacy statement does not apply to those linked websites. Each website should be checked for its own privacy statement. NaviNet is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of linked websites that are not administered by NaviNet

INFORMATION COLLECTION AND USE – NAVINET MULTI-PAYER PORTAL

NaviNet collects personal information when you register with NaviNet, when you use NaviNet products and services, and when you visit NaviNet pages or the pages of certain NaviNet partners from within the NaviNet portal. NaviNet may combine information about you that we have with information we obtain from business partners or other companies.

When you register, we ask for information such as your name, email address, and demographics. When you register with NaviNet and sign in to our services, you are not anonymous to us.

NaviNet collects information about your transactions with us and our business partners.

NaviNet uses information for the following general purposes:

·         Customize the content you see

·         Fulfill your requests for products and services,

·         Improve our services,

·         Allow NaviNet Products and Services to operate,

·         Contact you,

·         Conduct research, and

·         Provide anonymous reporting for internal and external clients.

NaviNet also may use this information now and in the future to introduce and market new products and services to existing customers.

INFORMATION-SHARING AND DISCLOSURE

NaviNet does not rent, sell, or share personal information about you with other people or our business partners, or non-affiliated companies except to provide products or services you've requested, when we have your permission, or under the following circumstances:

·         We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims.

·         We believe it is necessary to share information in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of NaviNet’s terms of use, or as otherwise required by law.

·         We transfer information about you if NaviNet is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, NaviNet will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY

We limit access to personal information about you to employees who we believe have a reasonable need to come into contact with that information to provide products or services to you or in order to do their jobs.

We have physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards that comply with federal regulations to protect personal information about you.

HOW YOU CAN CONTACT NAVINET FOR COMPLAINTS, QUESTIONS AND ENFORCEMENT OF THE POLICY

You can call NaviNet Customer Care at 1-888-482-8057
